{
  "questions" :[
    {
      "question": "What is the roles of scrum master in agile development method?",
      "answers": [
        "Protecting the team from outside interference and helps the team resolve issues or make improvements",
        "He maintains and communicates to all other participants a clear vision of what the Scrum team is trying to achieve",
        "Collaborates with internal and external stakeholders to gather and define the product backlog items",
        "The only authority responsible for what will be developed and in what order"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "For what kind purpose are used scenarios?",
      "answers": [
        "Describe a successful user experience",
        "Description of the normal flow of events and what can go wrong",
        "Tool used by engineers requirements",
        "All the answers are correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main difference in the process of collecting and analyzing requirements between following two methods of development: waterfall and agile ",
      "answers": [
        "There is no difference between the methods",
        "In agile the client can modify the requirements and add new requirements during the development process",
        "In agile it is not possible to start the development process before all the requirements have been collected and analyzed",
        "In waterfall the client can modify the requirements and add new requirements during the development process"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the types of tests? ",
      "answers": [
        "Structural tests and behavioral tests",
        "Black box testing and white box testing",
        "Alpha testing and beta testing",
        "User testing and system testing"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is TDD?",
      "answers": [
        "Tests are written before the code. Tests are part of the development process",
        "Each developer checks his own code",
        "An experienced testing team that checks the code at the completion of the development process",
        "Method that checks only the drivers of the progrem"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the differences between Walkthrough and Inspection",
      "answers": [
        "Walkthrough is more formal then walkthrough",
        "Inspection is more formal and more effective than Walkthrough",
        "walkthrough is mor formal and more effective than inspection",
        "Inspection is more effective then walkthrough"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What involves the preparation of a leader for review?",
      "answers": [
        "Determine what will be in the review",
        "Generate a list of comments",
        "Inspection",
        "All answers are incorrect"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a design pattern?",
      "answers": [
        "Singelton",
        "MVC",
        "MVVM",
        "All the answers are correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the use of SOA technology?",
      "answers": [
        "Create multiple platforms to work with a single product",
        "Allows working according to fixed protocols and is not flexible",
        "To combines the legacy technologies of a company with the newer technologies",
        "A technology that replaces all existing systems in an organization with a single system"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "How can an organization effectively reduce IT costs?",
      "answers": [
        "Replacing workers with other workers",
        "Layoffs",
        "Use private cloud",
        "Use a public cloud"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ron changed a feature in the system and as a result another part of the system does not work. What did Ron forget to do?",
      "answers": [
        "Regression testing",
        "User testing",
        "Release testing",
        "Black box testing"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the cases where SaaS is ineffective?",
      "answers": [
        "Applications using the web or mobile",
        "Applications where real-time data processing is required",
        "Vanilla Systems",
        "Tax collection systems"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question":"Flexibility,Adaptability and Security are all benefits of?",
      "answers": [
        "PaaS",
        "SaaS",
        "LaaS",
        "All the answers are correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "scorpion"
    },
    {
      "question": "Perform tests before releasing the system and after it has been released (in the customer's business), why?",
      "answers": [
        "Show the client that the code is working",
        "Make sure the customer is satisfied",
        "In case something was destroyed on the way to the customer",
        "Different types of servers in the developing company and the customer"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "scorpion"
    }
  ]
}
